

#### laurenmcelaney.design

linkedin.com/in/laurenmcelaney

mcelaneyl@gmail.com

818-568-6580

## LAUREN MCELANEY

## **SUMMARY**

I am a UI/UX Designer proficient in multimedia design and web design. I have experience in studying user behaviors which has allowed me to develop my skills with application development. I also have a strong background/interest in product design.

## **SKILLS**

Wireframing & Prototyping

Frontend Development

**Usability Testing** 

**Product Strategy** 

User Research & Testing

Persona & User Stories

Visual Design

UI/UX Design

## **TOOLS**

Figma

Sketch

Invision

Github

HTML & CSS

**Adobe Creative Suite** 

**Usability Hub** 

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Lauren Jeanne Photography 2007-Present

- · Founded fashion photography business
- · Assigned various test photo shoots for modeling agencies:

Ford Model Agency

Stars Model Management

JE Model Management

### **Sole Society**

Style and Service Specialist, 2017-2018

- · Provided customer support via emails, phone, and chat
- · Assisted on multiple projects throughout departments

#### Thrive Market

Member Services Specialist, 2017

- · Frontline representation of the company
- · Monitored all social media platforms
- · Solving all customer service requests in a high call and email environment

## **Poolside Concierge**

Web Designer, 2009-2011

- · Created and managed website content
- · Worked with the owner to recommend web copy for a target audience
- · Selected stock images and created original images for website
- · Updated entire site three times to account for expanding product and territory needs

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Bloc

User Experience Design Program, 2018-2019

Online program teaching the core principles of UI/UX design as well as frontend development for both desktop and mobile.

## **RECENT PROJECTS**

#### In The Cloud

Cloud based storage application.

#### Role:

- ·UI/UX
- ·Branding & Identity
- ·Visual Design

#### Solace

Mental health online community.

#### Role:

- ·UI/UX
- ·Branding & Identity
- ·Visual Design